Hey, guys.
( all greeting )
We need to talk to you
about something.
Yeah, we don't feel
like we can host Thanksgiving
this year.
What?!
Are you kidding?
Well, it's just with, uh, work
and the stress of adoption,
we don't feel like
we have the energy.
Plus, we don't think
it's fair
that every year
the burden falls on us.
That doesn't sound like you.
That's Monica talking!
No, no.
We made
this decision together.
She's putting words
in your mouth!
Don't you put words
in people's mouths.
You put turkey in
people's mouths.
I can't believe this.
This is Emma's
first Thanksgiving.
No, it's not.
It's not?
When was she born?
Well, personally,
I think it's great
you're giving yourself a break.
Thank you, Pheebs.
Sure. It's just as well.
I mean, last year
wasn't very good.
I think she's
losing her touch.
What?!
You are way off, lady!
Am I? Really?
Am I?
Well, why don't you cook
Thanksgiving dinner
and prove me wrong?
Well, think about it.
You'd be trying to top
what you did last year.
You'd be in a competition
with yourself.
That's my favorite kind.
Okay, we are
doing this!
Don't let yourself
get manipulated this way.
Stay out of
this, Chandler!
This is between me and me!
We are supposed to make
these decisions together.
Did you not watch the Dr. Phil
I taped for you?
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey.
Hi.
Happy Thanksgiving!
Oh, yeah, happy
Needless Turkey Murder Day.
Hey, guys, I ordered
some chocolate pies
from that bakery on Bleeker.
Could you pick them up for me?
You're not making
the pies yourself?
No, I don't make chocolate pies.
When I was younger,
I entered
this pie eating contest
and I ate so many
that just the thought of them
makes me sick.
Did you at least
win the contest?
Two minutes, 12 pies,
and a part of one tin.
Okay, I'll see you guys at 4:00.
Can't wait.
This dinner is going
to be so great.
In your face, Last Year Me!
Hey, Rach, what's
Emma doing today?
Well, let's see,
uh, I know
that she has a meeting
with her lawyer,
and then she has to make
a very big poop.
Why?
Well, I want to enter her
in a baby beauty pageant.
Oh, my God.
That's the creepiest thing
I've ever heard.
Okay, but
before you say no,
my friend Suzanne
is entering her kid
and compared to Emma,
she's a real dog.
Oh! Phoebe,
all babies are beautiful.
Uh, okay.
Just the idea
of pitting one baby
against another,
I mean, you know,
judging who's cuter
just for a trophy...
And $1,000.
...is something
I'm very interested in.
Oh, please,
do not tell Ross.
He still believes
that what's on the inside
is important.
Okay. Ooh, Emma needs
a cowgirl outfit
for the competition.
Where am I going to get
a cowgirl outfit
on Thanksgiving?
Well, I was thinking...
Take the clothes
off Joey's Cabbage Patch Kid!
Yeah.
( marching band playing )
( laughing )
Did someone drop
the baton again?
Why come all the way from Kansas
to do that?
I don't get older,
I just get better.
You know
what just occurred to me?
This could be
our last Thanksgiving
just the two of us.
I mean,
we could be getting a baby soon.
You don't know that.
Somebody's going to pick us.
Yeah, but we haven't heard
a thing
from the adoption agency,
and it's been weeks.
I'm telling you,
it's going to happen.
Next year, it's going
to be you, me
and little Hemingway Bing.
What? He's my favorite author.
Name one of his books.
The Firm?
Okay, let's see.
Okay, the turkey's in the oven;
the stuffing is ready...
You know, you always cook
this meal all by yourself.
Let me help this year.
Aw, Chandler,
that's sweet.
But you don't have
to do everything
Dr. Phil tells you to do.
I'm serious.
Let me do something.
Just not the turkey
or the stuffing.
Nothing high-profile.
Okay, let's see.
Oh, the cranberry sauce.
It's easy to make,
and no one
really cares about it.
Tell me more.
Okay, I'm going to go check
on something across the hall.
You start
by washing these.
Not with soap!
You obviously haven't tasted
my Palmolive potatoes.
Hey, hey, guess what Joey has?
Three tickets
to today's Rangers game!
Dude, I wanted him to guess.
Oh.
Oh, my God!
Yeah, they're
great seats, too.
Guess where they are.
Center ice.
Did I do something to you?
Mmm, the game's at 1:00.
ROSS:
So?
Dinner's at 4:00.
We'll never make it back.
We'll leave
before it's over.
We'll be back in time.
You say that now,
but it could take us
a long time to get back home.
Plus, Joey could get lost
and they could have to page us
to go pick him up.
Dude, two times
that happened!
Look, Monica's been working hard
all day.
She didn't want to host
this thing in the first place.
We shouldn't go.
He's right, man.
Yeah, I guess.
All right,
so we'll see you at 4:00.
Okay.
And get ready to taste
my very special cranberries.
Or should I say... Chanberries.
That's some gentle comedy,
dude.
We're still going
to the game, right?
Yeah.
Our next contestant
is a two-year-old.
Her name is Jacqueline,
and she comes from Mount Kisco.
Oh, Phoebe, listen,
I think we got to go.
This place is really
freaking me out.
I've been watching
this guy over there.
I don't think he
came with a kid.
But we can't leave now.
There was this one baby, Hayley,
who was favored to win,
and she got croup,
so she had to stay home.
This competition
just blew wide open, folks.
Phoebe, it's just too weird.
I just saw a one-year-old
running around
with pantyhose on.
I know. We should
have been more prepared.
It's okay.
Now, the way I see it,
our real competition now
is Cameron.
Oh, my God.
They just took
her sweater off.
Look at those arms.
Hello, Michelin man.
Oh, Phoebe!
Come on!
You know, it's
already 3:00.
They haven't even gotten
to Emma's group.
We got to go. We got dinner.
But Emma's got what it takes!
She could go all the way!
Phoebe, you have to calm down.
Okay, Rachel, the hottest
babies in the tri-state area
are in this room right now.
I overheard
one of the judges say
that not one of them
holds a candle to Emma.
Really?
Yeah.
You heard him say that?
All right. Okay.
All right,
let's give these babies
something to cry about.
Good! Okay!
Let's get down to business.
Emma needs some makeup.
What?!
She's going to look
all washed out
next to the other contestants.
Phoebe, I am not letting you
put makeup on my baby.
Why not?
Because I already did!
Oh! You bum!
Oh, you suck!
Get off the ice!
You idiot!
What a game!
I know!
I can't believe Chandler
is missing this.
Yeah, I'm sorry
he's not here too,
but I got to say,
I am really enjoying
Nacho Chair.
Yeah, I'd probably
enjoy it more
if you didn't keep
batting my hand away.
( yelling )
Oh, yeah!
These seats are great!
I know, I know.
When I was here
for Holidays on Ice...
I was sitting so far away,
Michelle Kwan
couldn't read my banner.
Whoa, hey, we better get going.
If we don't leave right now,
we're going
to be late for dinner.
Oh, but it's a tie game.
So, we're a little late,
you know?
The girls will be there.
Let's just stay
for one more goal.
I don't know.
One more fight.
Okay.
Where is everybody?
They're 45 minutes late.
I can't believe
they're not here.
I slaved and I slaved for what?
They've ruined Cranberry Day!
How late are we?
45 minutes.
Wow.
Here.
Okay.
Rachel and Phoebe
are already there, okay?
So, they probably started
without us.
We can just slip in,
and no one needs to know
where we were.
You may want to lose
the foam finger.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
You just want to put it
on your hand.
Hey.
( gasping )
Oh!
You're not at
Thanksgiving?
No!
No, we're late!
What are you
doing here?!
We're late, too!
( gasping and squealing )
We figured
we could be late
because you guys
would be on time.
Don't point that thing
at me, Tribbiani.
So, nobody's here?!
Monica's going
to kill us.
Yeah, where were you?
ROSS:
Yeah, what's
with the trophy?
Um, well, uh...
We were at
a spelling bee.
And I won!
You won an adult
Thanksgiving Day
spelling bee?
Yes. Y-E-S-- yes.
Let me see this.
"Grand Supreme Little Darling,
New York Division"?
That's me.
You entered Emma
in a beauty pageant?!
And it looks like
she put makeup on her.
Wait a second,
wait a second.
Where have I seen that
cowgirl outfit before?
I can't believe this.
She's our daughter.
That you would treat her
like some kind of show dog
is inexcusable!
She won $1,000!
So, this is
an annual thing?
( gasping )
That's Alicia May
Emory's outfit!
You guys,
there are people in there
who are not getting
any happier.
Yeah, what
are we going to do?
I don't know.
You guys figure it out.
I got to put Emma down
for her nap.
And Rach, while
you're in there,
throw something
on Alicia May!
All right,
what are we going to say?
Ooh! We'll say
that we were mugged.
You can't get mad
at someone who's been mugged.
Good, that's good.
But you don't look
like you were mugged.
No. Here.
Hey!
Do you hear something?
They're out there!
( gasping )
Let me see!
Oh, my God,
I can't believe this.
They're an hour late,
and they're just standing
out there talking!
Everything's so distorted.
It looks like Joey
has a giant hand.
That says Rangers on it.
They went to the game!
( gasping )
Oh, they are in
for a world of pain.
Ross' shirt is torn.
They're late,
and they're sloppy!
All right,
Emma's napping.
What happened
to your shirt?
I got mugged,
and they stole my pocket.
We're trying
to figure out
an excuse.
Hey, oh, how
about this?
We could say that
Monica told us
5:00, not 4:00.
That way, we're
right on time.
Or...!
we could plant PCP
in the apartment
and call the cops on her.
That would be a good way
to get rid of all the PCP
we have lying around.
We'll just say
that she said it was 5:00.
We'll just act casual.
We're not late.
We're right on time.
"We know you're out there."
( gasping )
( sotto voce ):
Who do you think
it's from?
Oh, God, this is bad.
This is so bad.
Well, let's just go in there
and face them.
Well, I'm not
going in first.
I bet that vein
on Monica's forehead
is popping like crazy.
Yeah, I hate that thing.
It's like a bolt
of lightning.
Oh, hey, I have an idea.
Why don't we play
Rock, Paper, Scissors,
and whoever loses
goes in first.
Okay.
All right,
I'm in.
Ready?
Ha, ha! I win!
What is that?
That's fire.
Beats everything.
Oh, really? Does it beat
water balloon?
( puncturing noise
and hissing )
Oh...
Well played, Phoebe
Buffay, well played.
All right, enough, come on.
Let's just go in
at the same time.
ALL:
Okay, okay.
It's locked.
Wha...? Oh, sure,
now they lock it,
but when they're having sex
on the couch, it's like,
"Come on in.
My butt is surprisingly hairy."
All right, come on.
All right, you guys!
We're so sorry
we're late!
Please let us in so we
can have dinner together.
No!
Everything's cold.
The turkey's dried out,
and the-the
stuffing's all soggy!
Yeah, and there's a bowl
of cranberry sauce that's...
What happens
to cranberry sauce?
Nothing. It's fine.
Oh, thank God!
Come on, you guys.
We're sorry.
Our-our subway broke down.
That's a lie!
You went to the game.
I can see Joey's hand.
For the love of
God, take it off!
You guys, come on.
It doesn't matter
why we're late.
We're all here now.
Please let us in so we can have
some of your delicious turkey.
( laughs )
I had a dream once about
a fax machine that did that.
That's all the turkey
you're going to get!
How are we going to
decide who gets this?
Water balloon!
What are we going to do?
I'm starving.
( gasps ):
Oh, I just remembered!
We do have
something to eat.
Monica put something in
our oven this morning.
Hey, you touch that,
and you will be sorry.
Guys, I'd listen to her.
The vein is bigger
than I've ever seen it!
Voila.
( laughs )
Oh, my God,
it's Brussels sprouts!
That's worse than no food!
Ha, ha! All you got
was Monica's stinky
Brussels sprouts!
Stinky?
Please let me stay on
this side of the door.
Oh, I know!
I still have my old key.
Ooh.
We can just unlock the door.
Well, I don't know if
that's such a good idea.
They clearly don't
want to be with us.
You know what?
I don't want to be
with them either,
but it's Thanksgiving,
and we should not want to be
together together!
If I could just get in there
and make a face-to-face apology,
you know,
look 'em in the eye,
I know can I get 'em
to forgive us.
I don't know...
I'm telling you...
I can do it.
Yeah, he can do it.
RACHEL:
Oh.
JOEY:
All right.
Oh...
It all looks so beautiful.
The turkey, the stuffing...
The cranberries.
( scoffs )
Enough! A monkey
could've made 'em!
Hey, listen, guys,
we feel really terrible.
He's doing that weird
eye-contact thing.
Don't look at him.
Come on, you guys.
We want you to know
we're very, very sorry.
Right, guys?
ROSS:
I feel terrible.
So sorry.
But let's not ruin this day.
You've worked so hard.
Let's move past this,
and try to have a nice meal
all together, huh?
The floating heads
do make a good point.
Yeah, they do seem
to feel pretty bad.
So bad.
Okay.
Okay, you two go get
the dessert,
and I'll let you in.
Dessert?
Yeah, I asked you and Phoebe
to pick up the pies.
You did remember, right?
Pies. Oh, we thought
you said "prize."
Here.
Grand Supreme Little Darling?
Congratulations!
Oh, my God,
you forgot the pies?!
Well, I can't believe this!
You forced me to make dinner,
then you're an hour late,
and you forget
the one little thing
that I asked you to do!
Really, girls, not cool.
Well, you man-heads
aren't any better.
You lied about going
to the game.
You knew it would make you late,
and you still went anyway.
Hey! I'm getting a little tired
of this, okay.
We said we're sorry!
It's Thanksgiving,
for Pete's sakes!
A day of forgiveness!
It's a day to be thankful.
Don't make me come up there.
Fine.
It's too late for apologies.
Let's just go.
I don't need your stupid dinner.
That would be a lot
more convincing if
you weren't drooling.
Ew! Is that what that is?
Sorry.
Come on, you guys.
Let's just do
our own Thanksgiving.
Yeah, I'll cook.
Yeah, let's go out.
Hey!
Yeah, you three
have a nice Thanksgiving.
Yeah.
The three of us?
You, Chan, and the vein!
( gasps )
( scoffs )
( gags )
Uh-oh. I'm stuck.
Joey, that is not going to work.
No, seriously.
I'm really wedged in here.
I'll pull you through.
Okay.
Ow, ow, ow, ow! Stop, stop!
I'm worried
about damaging my head.
It's a little late for that.
Well, hurry up.
You got to do something.
All right, well,
this does not change
anything.
Okay, we need
to get something
to grease the sides
of his face.
Uh, we got turkey grease.
Bring it.
I just want to say
that I'm sorry
I referred to the vein
as a separate person.
All right, here you go.
Okay.
Ooh, that smells good.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Okay, try it.
It isn't working!
All right, we're going
to have to unscrew the chain.
Well, hurry.
I can't feel my ears.
Can you ever feel your ears?
Interesting.
Chandler, where are
your tools?
Ooh, I left them
on my bulldozer.
I don't have tools.
Well, I do,
but Rachel borrowed them.
I lent them to Ross.
I gave them to Joey.
I left them at the park.
I'm finding it really hard
not to mess with him.
I've already stuffed
a bunch of Brussels
sprouts down his pants.
Nice.
( phone ringing )
Okay... I have to get that.
Now, when I get back,
I want you and your friends
to be gone.
Thanksgiving is over!
The vein has spoken!
It's really starting to hurt.
Okay, look, I'm... I'm
going to pull on the door,
and you guys push
as hard as you can.
Maybe we can get enough room
to wiggle him out, okay?
Okay, so push!
PHOEBE:
Just a sec.
We're kind of in the
middle of something here.
Oh! Stop putting things
down my pants!
Come on, guys, push!
Yeah, come on!
Push! Push! Push!
( grunts )
( screams )
RACHEL:
Oh!
My cranberries!
Oh, man, I got food all over me!
Ah! I can't believe
what you did!
Monica's going to kill you!
Look, look, look what the...
look what...
look, look, look what
floating heads did!
I don't care.
What's going on?
That was the adoption agency.
And...?
We're getting a baby!
Are you serious?!
There's a pregnant woman
in Ohio, and she picked us.
( all cheering )
I'm so happy for you.
This Thanksgiving kicks
last Thanksgiving's ass!
Whoo!
To Monica and
Chandler...
and that knocked-up girl
in Ohio.
Hear, hear.
I'm just so happy you guys
are finally getting a kid.
PHOEBE:
I know.
Have you considered
pageanting?
I can't believe they called.
We're actually getting a baby.
Oh, I know how you feel.
Really?
Sure. I went through
the exact same thing
with Alicia May Emory.
The waiting, the wondering...
then one day, I get that call
from Toys "R" Us.
She was in stock.
That is the exact same thing.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org